Cook, Alice Papers /3012
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Series Series VII: Publications and Writings
  - Sub-Series A. Publications
    - "International Comparisons: Problems and Research in the Industrialized World.", 1987 (Box 101, Folder 34)
      Chapter 12 in Working Women, Past, Present, Future by Karen Shallcross et al. Washington: Bureau of national Affairs, IRRA Series
    - Cook, Alice H. "An Amicus Brief.", 1986 (Box 101, Folder 35)
      NY: Cornell University, July 25, 1986
    - Cook, Alice H. "The International Labor Organization and Japanese Politics.", 1965 (Box 101, Folder 36)
      NY: Reprint Series No. 179, Cornell University. Originally published in Industrial and Labor Relations Review. Vol. 19, No. 1. October 1965.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Japanese Trade Unionism.", 1966 (Box 101, Folder 37)
      NY: Cornell University, May 1966.
    - Reviews, Advertising and Correspondence about the Manuscript/ Book "Japanese Trade Unionism" by Alice Cook, 1964-1970 (Box 101, Folder 37)
    - Windmuller, John P. "International Trade Union Organizations: Structure, Functions, Limitations.", 1967 (Box 101, Folder 38)
      NY: Reprint Series No. 235, Cornell University. Originally published in International Labor. New York: Harper and Row
    - Nevins, Thomas, and Cook Alice H. "Japan's Young Blue Collar Worker.", 1972 (Box 101, Folder 39)
      Unpublished. Industrial Relations: A Journal of Economy and Society. November 1972.
    - Nevins, Thomas, and Cook Alice H. "Japan's Young Blue Collar Worker.", 1972 (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - Correspondence from Industrial Relations: A Journal of Economy and Society to Alice Cook and Thomas Nevins. (Box 101, Folder 40)
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labor and Politics.", 1969 (Box 102, Folder 1)
      Originally Published in Issues in Industrial Society, Vol. 1, No. 2.
    - Hanson, Alice. "Labor and the Church.", 1940 (Box 102, Folder 2)
      The Crozer Quarterly. Vol. XVII, No. 3. July 1940. 171-179.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labor Education in the US: Marriage of Convenience?", 1980 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Garman, Phillips L. Review of Labor Education Outside the Unions by Alice H. Cook and Agnes M. Douty. (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Cook, Alice H., and Douty, Agnes M. "Labor Education Outside the Unions.", 1958 (Box 102, Folder 4)
      New York, State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University. June 1958.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labor, Management and Family Problems.", 1989 (Box 102, Folder 5)
      August 1, 1989.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labor Participation in Community Affairs: An Experiment in Adult Education.", 1955 (Box 102, Folder 6)
      ILR Research, Vol. 1, No. 2. March 1955. 8-9.
    - Cook, Alice H., Gray, Lois S. "Labor Relations in New York City.", 1966 (Box 102, Folder 7)
      NY: Reprint Series No. 191. Cornell University. Originally Published in Industrial Relations, a Journal of Economy and Society. Vol. 5, No. 3. May 1966.
    - Cook, Alice. "Labor Relations in Public Employment in NYC.", 1970 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labor Relations in the Public Service: A Unique Branch of Labor Relations Practice: The Japanese Case in Local Government.", 1969 (Box 102, Folder 9)
      NY: Reprint Series No. 289, Cornell University. Originally published in The Changing Patterns of Industrial Relations in Asian Countries.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labor Relations in the Public Service: A Unique Branch of Labor Relations Practice: The Japanese Case in Local Government.", 1969 (Box 102, Folder 10)
      The Monthly Journal of the Japanese Institute of Labour. Vol. 11, No. 8. August 1969.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labors Role in COmmunity Affairs.", 1955 (Box 102, Folder 11)
      NY: State School of Industrial and Labor Relations, Cornell University. Bulletin 32. August 1955.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labor's Search for it's Place in the Community; The Role of a Professional Community Consultant.", 1955 (Box 102, Folder 12)
      The Journal of Educational Sociology, Vol. 29, No. 4. December 1955. 173-183.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labor's Search for it's Place in the Community; The Role of a Professional Community Consultant.", 1955 (Box 102, Folder 12)
      Reprinted from The Journal of Educational Sociology, Vol. 29, No. 4. December 1955. 173-183.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Maternity Benefits.", 1975 (Box 102, Folder 13)
      United States National Committee Bulletin. Vol. 8, No. 3. October 1975. 1- 4.
    - Merger articles between the AFL and the CIO, Notes and Correspondence (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Newspaper articles on the merger between the AFL and the CIO (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Cook, Alice H., and Lorwin, Val R. "The Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions in Four European Countries.", 1980 (Box 102, Folder 16)
      Program in Sex Roles and Social Change, Center for the Social Sciences, Columbia University. New York City. October 16, 1980.
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions in Four European Countries.", 1980 (Box 102, Folder 16)
      NATO Conference on Women and Work. Lisbon. August 1980.
    - Magazine and newspaper articles about unemployment (Box 102, Folder 17)
    - Notes and articles about women and working (Box 102, Folder 18)
    - Cook, Alice. "Union Education.", 1979 (Box 102, Folder 19)
      Chapter three. November 1979
    - Cook, Alice. "Women in Union Structures." (Box 102, Folder 20)
      Chapter four
    - Cook, Alice, Till-Retz, et al. "Equal Pay and Equal Opportunity: Collective Bargaining and Government Action." (Box 102, Folder 21)
      Chapter five
    - Cook, Alice, Till-Retz, et al. "Collective Bargaining and Government Action.", 1980 (Box 102, Folder 22)
      Chapter 5. September 25, 1980
    - Cook, Alice, Till-Retz, et al. "Equal Pay.", 1980 (Box 102, Folder 23)
      Chapter 6. April 1980
    - Background information for Chapter 6 (Box 102, Folder 24)
    - Background information for Chapter 6 (Box 102, Folder 25)
    - Cook, Alice. "Regular Voluntary Part-time Work." (Box 102, Folder 26)
      Chapter 9. May 1, 1985.
    - Correspondence Book I Publication (Box 102, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1976 (Box 102, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1979 (Box 102, Folder 29)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 102, Folder 30)
    - Correspondence, 1980 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1981 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence, 1982 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Dissemination, 1977-1979 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Cook, Alice. "Women and Trade Unions in Five Countries.", 1977 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      Interim Report to the German Marshall Fund. February 15, 1977.
    - Cook, Prof. Alice H., Lorwin, Prof. Val R., et. al. "Trade Union Policies and Programs: A Comparative Study of Women in the Labor Market and in Politics in Seven Western Societies." (Box 103, Folder 6)
      plus correspondence
    - "Study of Women Working Abroad.", 1977 (Box 103, Folder 7)
      ILR Report. Spring 1977. 32.
    - "Five Year Report 1972-1977." (Box 103, Folder 7)
      The German Marshall Fund of the United States: A Memorial to the Marshall Plan.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Employment Policies by Unions." (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Cook, Alice H. "Problems and Policies Concerning Women Reentering the Labor Market.", 1975 (Box 103, Folder 8)
      Nov-75
    - Expense lists, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence on the German Marshall Fund Project, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - German Marshall Fund Project, 1976-1978 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Misc. Correspondence about Italy, 1976-1978 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Misc. Correspondence about Israel, 1980-1981 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Newspaper and magazine articles, 1979-1980 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Misc. Bad Homburg, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Project Questionnaire, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Outline for German Marshall Fund Project, 1976 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Cook, Alice H., Lorwin, Val R., et al. "Trade Unions and Women in Five European Countries.", 1976 (Box 103, Folder 18)
      A Proposal for a Project to Study. June 9, 1976
    - Correspondence about a Washington/NYC Meeting, 1977 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence Book II- Post Bellagio?, 1979-1981 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence Book II- Post Bellagio?, 1979-1984 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Foulmatter of "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Foulmatter, continued, of "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 23)
    - Foulmatter, continued, of "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 24)
    - Foulmatter, continued, of "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 25)
    - Gallerys of "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 26)
    - Gallerys of "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 27)
      Beginning-146
    - Gallerys of "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 28)
      147-287
    - Next set of Gallerys for "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 29)
      Beginning-80
    - Next set of Gallerys for "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 30)
      81-190
    - Next set of Gallerys for "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 31)
      191-287
    - Final Copy of Book II (Box 103, Folder 32)
      Foreword-Chapter 3
    - Final Copy of Book II (Box 103, Folder 33)
      Chapters 4-6
    - Final Copy of Book II (Box 103, Folder 34)
      Chapters 7-10, References, Periodicals, and Glossary
    - Two Boxes of 5.5 Inch Hard Disks Containing "A Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions." (Box 103, Folder 35-36)
    - Cook, Alice H. "Mothers Working.", 1977 (Box 104, Folder 1)
      Cornell Alumni News. November 1977. 28-29.
    - Cook, Alice H. "New Goals for Labor Education.", 1957 (Box 104, Folder 2)
      Adult Leadership, Vol. 6, No. 4. October, 1957. 108-109, 114.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Political Action and Trade Unions: A Case Study of the Coal Miners in Japan.", 1967 (Box 104, Folder 3)
      Monumenta Nipponica, Vol. 22, Nos. 1-2. 1967. 103-121.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Labor and Politics." (Box 104, Folder 4)
      Issues in Industrial Society: Political Activities of Unions and Company Managers, Vol. 1, No.2. 16-22.
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Politics of Compensation.", 1986 (Box 104, Folder 5)
      June, 1986
    - Cook, Alice H. "Public Employee Bargaining in New York City.", 1970 (Box 104, Folder 6)
      NY, Cornell University, Reprints No. 290. Originally Published in Industrial Relations, Vol. 9, No. 3. May, 1970.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Public Policies to Help Dual-Earner Families Meet the Demands of the Work World.", 1989 (Box 104, Folder 7)
      Industrial and Labor Relations Review, Vol. 42, No. 2. January 1989.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Public Policies That Can Aid Dual-Earner Families." (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Representation of Women and Their Interests in Industrial Relations and Institutions: Women in Trade Unions.", 1978 (Box 104, Folder 8)
      Institute of Labor Studies. 1978
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Root of the Matter: Needed Changes in the Labor Market." (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Cook, Alice H. "Rose Golden: Recollections and Reminders.", 1991 (Box 104, Folder 10)
      RKG Conference. September 20, 1991.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Rose's Writing.", 1992 (Box 104, Folder 11)
      Cornell University Library Archives. April 20, 1992.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Sex Discrimination at Universities: An Ombudsman's View.", 1972 (Box 104, Folder 12)
      Reprinted from American Association of University Professors Bulletin, Vol. 58, No. 3. September 1972.
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Status of Working Women.", 1968 (Box 104, Folder 13)
      American Labor Review, Vol. 7, No. 1. January, 1968. 13-17. (Printed in Japanese)
    - Interview with Dr. Alice H. Cook, associate professor of trade unionism in the New York School of Industrial and Labour Relations, Cornell University. "Successful Methods in Workers Education.", 1966 (Box 104, Folder 14)
      American Labour Review. October 1966. 15-17.
    - Cook, Alice H. Address. Tasteful Ladies., 1989 (Box 104, Folder 15)
      Ithaca Commons, Ithaca NY. July 28, 1989.
    - Cook, Alice H. "A Statement of Purpose and Plans for a Long-term Project on Trade Union Government.", 1959 (Box 104, Folder 16)
      November 6, 1959.
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Trade Union Movement and Working Women.", 1978 (Box 104, Folder 17)
      World Congress of Sociology Working Group 7: Women's Movements. International Sociological Association. Uppsala, Sweden. August 14-19, 1978.
    - Notes, Book Reviews, and Correspondence on the book Union Democracy: Practice and Ideal (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Cook, Alice H. "Women and American Trade Unions.", 1968 (Box 104, Folder 19)
      NY: Reprint Series No. 237. Originally published in The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science, Vol. 375. January 1968.
    - Cook, Alice H. Address to the Commander of the Seneca Army Depot., 1983 (Box 104, Folder 20)
      Upstate Ladies for Peace. Seneca NY. October 2, 1983. Includes a Newspaper Clipping of Alice Cook.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Women and American Trade Unions." (Box 104, Folder 21)
      The Annals of the American Academy of Political and Social Science.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Women and Minorities.", 1991 (Box 104, Folder 22)
      Chapter 7 in the IRRA Yearbook on Trade Unions. 1991.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Women and Unions: Cause for Celebration?", 1981 (Box 104, Folder 23)
      ILR Convocation. September 7, 1981.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Women and Work in Industrial Societies: Where We Are and Where We Are Going.", 1980 (Box 104, Folder 24)
      NY: Cornell University. June, 1980.
    - Cook, Alice H., and Ratner, Ronnie Steinberg. "Women, Unions, and Equal Employment Opportunity.", 1980 (Box 104, Folder 25)
      National Commission on Employment Policy. September, 1980.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Work and Family.", 1989 (Box 104, Folder 26)
      Speech before the Hawaii Commission on the status of Women, Working Women of Hawaii, and the YWCA. Honolulu, Hawaii. March 22, 1989.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Work and Family: A Collision Course?", 1987-1988 (Box 104, Folder 27)
      ILR Review. 1987-1988.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Work and Changing Family Needs: Can They Be Accommodated?", 1988 (Box 104, Folder 28)
      July 1988.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Work and Family: An Overview of Theories and Problems.", 1987 (Box 104, Folder 29)
      IIRA Panel on Work and Family. Israel. December 13, 1987.
    - Paragraph on Alice Hanson. Workers' Education in the United States, Theodore Brameld, Editor., 1941 (Box 104, Folder 30)
      NY: Harper & Brothers Publishers. 1941. 318.
    - Hanson, Alice. "Action and Study: Some Representative Examples of Workers' Education Programs.", 1941 (Box 104, Folder 30)
      Chapter 6 in Workers' Education in the United States, Theodore Brameld, Editor. NY: Harper & Brothers Publishers. 1941.
    - United States. Office of Military Government for Germany. Workers Education in the U.S. Zone (Germany), 1947 (Box 104, Folder 31)
      Visiting Expert Series No. 1. By Alice Hanson Cook. Manpower Division. Berlin: APO 742. Germany: June 1947.
    - United States. Office of Military Government for Germany. Workers Education in the U.S. Zone of Germany Since the Beginning of Occupation., 1947 (Box 104, Folder 32)
      By Alice Hanson Cook. Manpower Division. Berlin: APO 742. Germany: June 26, 1947.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Working Women: European Experience and American Need.", 1977 (Box 104, Folder 33)
      NY: Cornell University Reprint Series No. 431. Originally in Joint Economic Committee Congress of the United States: American Workers in a Full Employment Economy. September 15, 1977. 95th Congress, 1st Session.
    - Hanson, Alice. "Workers Education on the March.", 1939 (Box 104, Folder 34)
      Reprinted from American Teacher. April, 1939.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Working Women in Japan.", 1981 (Box 104, Folder 35)
      New York Conference on Asian Studies. Hartwick College. Oneonta, NY. October 9-10, 1981.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Approaches to pay Equality in the United States.", 1985 (Box 104, Folder 36)
      Excerpted from Comparable Worth: A Casebook of Experiences in States and Localities. Honolulu: Industrial Relations Center, University of Hawaii, 1985.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Comparable Worth: The Challenges, Approaches and Experiences of Implementation.", 1984 (Box 104, Folder 36)
    - Cook, Alice H. "Equality in the Workplace: The Role of Trade Unions in Market Economics.", 1982 (Box 104, Folder 36)
      Ithaca, NY. 1982
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Effects on the Structure of Society of the Growing Number of Women in the Work force.", 1979 (Box 104, Folder 36)
      College Board National Forum. New Orleans, Louisiana. October 30, 1979.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Incomparable Worth: The Cost of Women's Work.", 1987 (Box 104, Folder 37)
      Villanova University. September 23, 1987.
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions in Four European Countries.", 1980 (Box 104, Folder 37)
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Most Difficult Revolution: Women and Trade Unions.", 1980 (Box 104, Folder 37)
      Equal Opportunities International. Vol. 1, No. 2. 1980
    - Cook, Alice H. "Problems and Possibilities in the Comparative Study of Working Women.", 1988 (Box 104, Folder 38)
      University of Kansas. April, 1988.
    - Cook, Alice H, and Hayashi, Hiroko. "Resistance and Reform in Japan: The Courts and Discrimination Against Working Women.", 1978 (Box 104, Folder 38)
      Uppsala, Sweden. 1978.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Working Women in Japan.", 1980 (Box 104, Folder 39)
      A summary of the study Working Women in Japan: Discrimination, Resistance and Reform. NYSSILR, Cornell University, 1980.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Working Women in Japan.", 1981 (Box 104, Folder 39)
    - Cook, Alice H. "The Politics of Compensation.", 1986 (Box 104, Folder 39)
      ANA Convention. Anaheim, CA. June, 1986.
    - Cook, Alice H. "Work and Family: An Overview of Theories and Problems.", 1987 (Box 104, Folder 39)
      IIRA Panel on Work and Family. Israel. December 13, 1987
    - The Kirkus Reviews, 1985 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev. of Women Workers in Fifteen Countries, Jennie Farley ed. THE KIRKUS REVIEWS. New York: June 1, 1985.
    - Wertheimer, Barbara M. (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev. of From Sky Girl to Flight Attendant: Women and the Making of a Union, by Georgia Panter Nielsen. The Journal of American History. (Alice Cook did the introduction to From Sky Girl...)
    - Cook, Alice H. Rev. of The Invisible Work Force: Transforming American Business with Outside and Home-based Workers by Beverly Lorenzo., 1990 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      ILR Review. January, 1990.
    - Farley, Jennie (ed.). Women workers in Fifteen Countries., 1983 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      ILR Press. (description of) A book assembled for the 1983 conference given at Cornell University in honor of Alice Cook's 80th birthday.
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev. of Comparable Worth, Pay Equity, and Public Policy, Rita Mae Kelly, and Jane Bayes eds. NY: Cornell University
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev. of Women and Information Technology, by Marilyn J. Davidson and Cary L. Cooper, eds. NY: Cornell University.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1989 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev. of Doing Comparable Worth: Gender, Class and Pay Equality, by Joan Acker, and Wage Justice: Comparable Worth and the Paradox of Technocratic Reform, by Sara M. Evans, and Barbara J. Nelson. NY: ILRRev. November, 1989.
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev. of Madam Secretary: Frances Perkins, a Biography of America's First Woman Cabinet Member, by George Martin. NY: Cornell University.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1989 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev. of Alternative Work Schedules, by Jon L. Pierce, John Newstrom, et al. ILR Review. December, 1989.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1987 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Red. of A Comparable Worth Primer, by Steven L. Willborn. ILR Review. February 17, 1987.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1905-1925 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev. of Origins of Protective Labor Legislation for Women, 1905-1925, by Susan Lehrer. American Journal of Sociology. 676-677.
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev of The World of Women's Trade Unionism: Comparative Historical Essays, Norbert C. Solden ed. NY: Cornell University.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1988 (Box 104, Folder 40)
      Rev. of A New Deal for Workers' Education: The Workers' Service Program, by Joyce L. Kornbluh. ILR Review. July, 1988.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1985 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Japanese Women: Constraint and Fulfillment, by Takie Sugiyama. ILR Review. May 1985
    - Cook, Alice H., 1983 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Organized Workers and Socialist Politics in Interwar Japan, by Steven S. Large. ILR Review. October 1983
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Work and Lifecourse in Japan, by David W. Plath ,ed. ILR Review.
    - Rozen, Frieda S., 1983 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Women Workers in Fifteen Countries, Jennie Farley ed.. Library Journal. A book assembled for the 1983 conference given at Cornell University in honor of Alice Cook's 80th birthday
    - Thornton, Margaret, 1984 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Comparable Worth: The Problem and States' Approaches to Wage Equity, by Alice Cook. The Journal of Industrial Relations. June 1984.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1985 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Women, Work & Protest: A Century of Women's Labor History, by Ruth Milkman. ILR Review December 26, 1985
    - Cook, Alice H., 1982 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of The New Nightingales: Hospital Workers, Unions, New Women's Issues, by Patricia Cayo Sexton. ILR Review. October, 1982
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Women Returning to Work: Policies and Progress in Five Countries, by Alice M. Yohalem, ed. NY: Cornell University
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of The Politics of Women and Work in the Soviet union and the United States: Alternative Work Schedules and Sex Discrimination, by Joel C. Moses. Contemporary Sociology. University of Minnesota.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1986 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Working In Hawaii: A Labor History, by Edward D. Beechhert. ILR Review. August 1986
    - Frantzve, Jerri, 1983 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Women Workers in Fifteen Countries, Jennie Farley ed.. Personal Psychology. 492-494. A book assembled for the 1983 conference given at Cornell University in honor of Alice Cook's 80th birthday.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1986 (Box 104, Folder 41)
      Rev. of Reconceiving Part-Time Work: New Perceptions for Older Workers and Women, by Hilda Kahne. ILR Review. December 1986.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1974 (Box 104, Folder 42)
      Rev. of The Politics of Labor Legislation in Japan, by Ehud Harari. February, 1974
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 42)
      Rev. of Discrimination in Employment, by Folke Schmidt ed. NY: Cornell University
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 42)
      Rev. of Trade Unions as a Pressure Group in the European Community, by Emil Joseph Kirchner. NY: Cornell University
    - Cook, Alice H. (Box 104, Folder 42)
      Rev. of Comparative Union Democracy: Organization and Opposition in British and American Unions, by J. David Edelson, and Malcolm Warner. American Journal of Sociology, Vol. 84, No. 5. 1287-1289.
    - Cook, Alice H., 1976 (Box 104, Folder 42)
      Rev. of Women in Changing Japan, by Joyce Lebra. NY: Cornell University. 1976
    - Cook, Alice H., 1972 (Box 104, Folder 42)